Guide to the Yoshio Kishi and Irene Yah-Ling Sun Collection 1860-2010 MSS.292
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Oversize Series IV: Hollywood Films, Television, Theater and Actors
  - Subseries A: Film
    - "Les Tribulations d'un Chinois en Chine" - French movie poster (3'11"x5'3"), Undated (Folder 20)
    - Life Magazine, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Movie posters - photocopied, Undated (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Movie posters (medium sized) - "7 Women from Hell" (1961); "The Brides of Fu Manchu" (1966); "Chicano Film Festival" (1980); "Cinema East"; "Come See the Paradise" (1990); "Ghost of the China Sea" (1958); "Glædernus Hus"; "Satan Never Sleeps" (1962), 1958-1990 (Folder 18)
    - Movie Posters (One Sheets) - "The Bamboo Prison" (1954); "Boston Blackie's Chinese Venture" (1949); "The Camp on Blood Island" (1958); Captured in Chinatown"; "Chan is Missing" (1982); "Chinatown" (1974), 1949-1982 (Folder 21)
    - Movie posters (One Sheets) - "Chinatown at Midnight" (1949); "The Crimson Kimono" (1959); "The Fiendish Plot of Dr. Fu Manchu" (1980); "House of Bamboo" (1960); "Lady from Chung King"; "M Butterfly" (1993), 1949-1993 (Folder 22)
    - Movie posters (One Sheets) - "Scorched Earth"; "The Temple of Dusk"; "Trader Tom of the China Seas" (1954); "Walk Like a Dragon" (1960); "When Were You Born?" (1938), 1938-1960 (Folder 23)
    - "Mulan" movie poster, undated (Folder 3)
    - "The Mysterious Dr. Fu Manchu" movie poster, Undated (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - News articles about film / movies, 1920-1921 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - "Prisoner of War" movie posters, 1954 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Reel Life: A Magazine of Moving Pictures, 1914 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - "Sayonara" movie poster, 1956 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - "Sayonara" movie poster, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - "Screen and Stage" pages (in Japanese), 1925 (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - "The Secret of Blood Island" movie poster, Undated (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - "The Shadow" movie poster, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Show Magazine, 1962, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - "There Still is Only One King Kong" advertisement reprint, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - "Tora! Tora! Tora!" movie poster, Undated (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - "The World of Suzie Wong" movie poster, Undated (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - "The Yellow Menace" 16 episode serial, Undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Subseries B: Theater
    - Benefit Concert to Ais Indochinese Refugees - poster, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - "Cold Tofu" - improvisational comedy group poster, Undated (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - East West Players - Hokusai Sketchbooks - poster, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - "Emi Hatano: Modern Dance Recital" poster, Undated (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - "Flower Drum Song" poster, Undated (Roll-storage Shared Fales 038)
    - "The Grand Kabuki" - National Theatre of Japan - poster, Undated (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - "The Grand Kabuki" - National Theatre of Japan - poster, Undated (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - "The Grand Kabuki" at the National Theatre of Japan - programs, 1977, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Korean National Folk Company - poster, Undated (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Kyogen: National Comic Theatre of Japan - poster, Undated (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - "M. Butterfly" poster, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - National Puppet Theatre of Japan: Bunraku - poster, Undated (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - National Shadow Theatre of Malaysia - poster, Undated (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Noh-Kyogen - National Theatre of Japan - poster, Undated (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Noh National Theatre of Japan - Beacon Theater poster, Undated (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - "Once is Never Enough" poster - Pan-Asian Repertory Theatre, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - "Pacific Overtures" poster, c. 1984 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - "Pacific Overtures" poster, Undated (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Programs and articles - mixed, Undated (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - "Shiro: A Musical Fantasy" poster, Undated (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - "Song of Singapore" poster, Undated (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Theatre Magazine, 1927 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Subseries C: Actors
    - Hayakawa, Sessue, Undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Hayakawa, Sessue - film stills, Undated (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Images of Asian American Actors, Undated (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Japanese article - unidentified actors, 1931 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Japanese article - various actors, 1935 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Lee, Bruce - poster, Undated (Folder 24)
    - Look Magazine - "World's Most Beautiful Chinese Girl" (Anna May Wong), 1938 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, Undated (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Tanaka, Michiko (Japanese article), 1935 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Tsuru Aoki, Undated (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Wong, Anna May, Undated (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Wong, Anna May - clippings, Undated (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Wong, Anna May - film stills, articles, etc..., Undated (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Wong, Anna May - mounted photograph, Undated (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Wong, Anna May - movie posters, Undated (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Wong, Anna May - pictures, Undated (Box 47, Folder 19)
- Oversize Series V: Literature
  This series contains the oversize material from "Series V: Literature".
  - "The Adventures of Tintin: The Blue Lotus" - L.A. Times Book Review, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - "Our Home is the Sea" by Riki Levenson - book promotion poster, Undated (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Tsukiyama, Gaik - book advertisement, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - "Yellowfish" by John Keeble - dust jacket, Undated (Box 52, Folder 22)
- Oversize Series VI: Yoshio Kishi's Files
  This series contains the oversize material from "Series VI: Yoshio Kishi Files".
  - Subseries B: Collected Articles
    - The Arts magazine, 1946 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - "China in America: A Study in the Social Life of the Chinese", 1887 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Du Magazine, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - The Japan Weekly Mail, 1892 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - "La Chinoise" - by De Keyser, 1938 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Mixed collected articles, 1974-1988, Undated (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Mixed collected articles, Undated (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - The New York Times, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - The Sphere - "Reaping the Whirlwind: Sir Robert Hart's Prophecy of a Yellow Peril", 1900 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - "When East was East in the Old West" - Gross, Helen Rocca, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Subseries C: Notes
    - Fogg Art Museum calendar, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Subseries F: Subject Files
    - Modern Photography - silk engraving of "The Season at Niagra Falls", Undated (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Ngo Vinh Long - poem - printed on poster, Undated (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - Otsuka - "The Dance of the Twelve Kimonos" print, Undated (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Reiss, Winold - "To Color America: Portraits by Winold Reiss" National Portrait Gallery exhibition poster, 1990 (Folder 17)
    - Stonetone - portfolio of lithographic prints, Undated (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Sugimoto, Henry - "Guard Tower" print, inscribed to Yoshio, Undated (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Sugimoto, Henry - print of woman with baby, Undated (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Sugimoto, Henry - signed poster, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Subseries G: Scrutable Image
    - "Acupuncture" poster; "Dutch Treats: Switch from What You're Used To" ad poster, Undated (Folder 25)
    - Dutch Treats Cigars - subway advertisement, Undated (Box 53, Folder 31)
    - Japanese caligraphy poster, Undated (Folder 26)
    - Matted Photographs by Kishi (1 of 8), Undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Matted Photographs by Kishi (2 of 8), Undated (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Matted Photographs by Kishi (3 of 8), Undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Matted Photographs by Kishi (4 of 8), Undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Matted Photographs by Kishi (5 of 8), Undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Matted Photographs by Kishi (6 of 8), Undated (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Matted Photographs by Kishi (7 of 8), Undated (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Matted Photographs by Kishi (8 of 8), Undated (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Looney Toons "Creation of Adam" poster, Undated (Roll-storage Shared Fales 038)
    - McDonald's "McNugget Imperial Package" banner, Undated (Flat-file-folder TBD)
    - Photographs of various Japanese-American ceremonies, c. 1930s (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Portraits of Nancy Graves, Ron Vawter, Tony Vasconcellos, David Warrilow, Undated (Folder 19)
- Unprocessed Printed Ephemera and Materials, 1999-2009 (Box 90)